+91 8700354328

Irshadali644@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/irshad-ansari-16922b117/

https://portfolio-irshad.netlify.app/

# **Irshad Ansari**

## **Summary**

My name is Md. Irshad Ansari, and I am a Front-End software developer with a degree from Vinoba bhave university. With four years of experience in the software development industry.

My primary area of expertise is in JavaScript, React JS, HTML, CSS, and Bootstrap, and I have extensive experience in designing and developing responsive web applications.

## **Certifications**

#### **Programming Languages:**

- JavaScript
- Redux.js
- Git
- HTML5
- Tailwind CSS

- React.js
- jQuery
- Bootstrap
- CSS

# **Skill Highlights**

- Project management
- Strong decision maker
- Complex problem solver

- Creative design
- Innovative
- Service-focused

# **Experience**

### Sr. UI Developer

McCoy Mart

Nov 2020 - Present (3 Years)

- Cooperate with designers to create clean interfaces and simple, intuitive interactions and experiences.
- Develop project concepts and maintain optimal workflow.
- Work with senior developer to manage large, complex design projects for corporate clients.

## UI Developer Seabird Logisolutions Limited

22nd April, 2019 to 30th Apr, 2020. (1 year)

- My primary responsibilities as a Front-End Developer, ensuring that the web pages are optimized for maximum performance and usability, and writing clean, well-organized, and reusable code.
- The knowledge I have gained as a new developer on web application development, new frameworks, and also how to work in an office environment is splendid.
- Work with senior developer to manage large, complex design projects for corporate clients.

## **Education**

#### **R.V.S School**

Matriculation 2003-2004

#### **Bokaro Schools**

Intermediate of science (I. SC) 2004–2006

#### **V.B.U University**

Bachelor of Science(B.SC) 2006 – 2011

### **Capital University Jharkhand**

Pursuing MCA